{"data":[{"question":"Salt lake city, Utah's capital and largest city, is industrial and banking center.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"capital ","b":"largest ","c":"is industrial ","d":"center","answer":"3","explain":"- Is industrial-> is an industrial","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The arthropods, including insects and spiders, are great economic and medical significance.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"including ","b":"are great ","c":"economic ","d":"significance","answer":"2","explain":"- Are great-> have great","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The research of Percy Juliar has contributed to the creation of drugs that are in widespread use over victims of arthritis.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of ","b":"creation ","c":"in ","d":"over ","answer":"3","explain":"- In->x","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"To his rural neighbors, Robert Frost was an likely farmer who wrote poets late at night.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"To his rural neighbors","b":"an likely farmer ","c":"who wrote poets ","d":"late at night","answer":"3","explain":"- Who wrote poets-> who wrote poems","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The walls of this chapel are of solid masonry twenty-two and a half foot high and four feet thick.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"of this chapel ","b":"are ","c":"foot ","d":"four feet ","answer":"3","explain":"- Foot-> of foot","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The weeks of summer training are often as tense for sports writers as it is for football players and coaches.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"are often ","b":"as ","c":"tense for ","d":"it is ","answer":"4","explain":"- It is-> they are","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"Maritime law regulates commerce and navigation on the seas or other navigable waters, including inland lake rivers.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"regulates commerce ","b":"other ","c":"including ","d":"lake rivers","answer":"4","explain":"- Lake rivers-> lakes and rivers","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"In all of the workers' union, they had definite and detailed rules about pension.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"all of ","b":"workers' union","c":"they had ","d":"detailed rules ","answer":"3","explain":"- They had-> they have","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"The tartar chief controls a thousand men, all of them must obey his orders in both war and peace.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"controls ","b":"them ","c":"his ","d":"in both ","answer":"1","explain":"- Controls-> controlled","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"},{"question":"In the Middle Ages, books called bestiaries were prepared in an attempt to describe animals, real or imagine, that exemplified human traits.\n\u00a0\n\u00a0","a":"called ","b":"an attempt ","c":"real or imagine","d":"that ","answer":"3","explain":"- Real or imagine-> reality or imagine","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"26","subcategorylv2":"23","type":"1"}]}